

PORTFOLIO

HTTPS://TRUPTI7291.GITHUB.IO/PORTFOLIO/

CONTACT

♠ BLUMENTSTR. 11, 24937 FLENSBURG

TRUPTIKARA@GMAIL.COM

in HTTPS://WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/TRUPTIH/

+49 (0) 17686968270

FULL - STACK SKILLS

Front-end:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, React, React Native, Angular

Back-end:

MongoDB, Express, React, Node

Dev tools

Github, Postman, Shell, VS Code, Atom

LANGUAGES

•••• German (B1)

•••• English

•••• Gujarati - Mothertongue

•••• Hindi

SKILLS

 Software: MS Office, Tally

 Strength: Communication skills and Positive attitude

INTERESTS

- I enjoy reading nonfiction/fiction books.
- I like Traveling and long walks
- I like playing in codepen

TRUPTI HIRANI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Full-stack web developer based in Flensburg, Germany with experience in Front Desk Reception, Documenting patient's internal/external lab tests, hands-on experience in the pathology laboratory, Records Management, and MERN stack as a developer. I use React Native, Mongoose, MERN on top of basic HTML, CSS, SCSS / SASS, and Javascript. I develop both on the Front and Back -end, but my focus is front as I can use my existing knowledge about user flow and user journey to develop efficient and easy-to-use programs.

PROJECTS

CareerFoundry

Chat Application

Jan 2022 - Feb 2022

- Developed a chat app for mobile devices using React Native. The app will provide users with a chat interface and options to share images and their location.
- The app is developed using Expo. Chat conversations are stored in Google Firestore Database.

CareerFoundry

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

myFlix Application

- Developed a client-side application developed in React, based on its existing server-side code using MERN stack.
- The API is tested in Postman and deployed to Heroku.

EXPERIENCE

MMPJ Hospital - Bhuj, India

Jan 2013 - April 2018

Computer Operator

 Laboratory Reports & Spreadsheets preparation, Data Entry, Documenting patient's external lab tests, E-mails checkup, hand-on experience in a pathology laboratory, Database & Records Management

MMPJ Hospital - Bhuj,India

Jun 2012 - Dec 2012

RECEPTIONIST

 Telephone & Front Desk Reception, Customer/Patient Service, Executive & Administrative Support, Complaint Handling

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry, Germany

JULY 2021 - MARCH 2022

JUNE 2009 - JUNE 2012

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT (WEITERBILDUNG)

Full-stack Web Development Bootcamp with immersive and rigorous software development training. Course included coding projects in HTML, CSS, vanilla Javascript, JQuery, React Native, Redux, Node.js, Angular. Program course also integrated building a RESTful API, Web server Frameworks, Relational & Non-Relational Databases.

Gujarat University, Ahmedabad, India

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION (BCA)

Studied various languages like C, C++, Database Management System, VB.net.